A Guide to the Records of WRVA Radio Station 1925-1968
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Series I: Daily Events Files
  - Listeners' Mail 1960 (Box 19)
  - Miscellaneous Mail 1960 (Box 19)
  - NBC Correspondence 1960 (Box 19)
  - WRB Personal 1960 (Box 20)
    A27-7U
  - QSL Reception Reports 1960 June-Dec (Box 20)
  - QSL Reception Reports 1960 March-May (Folder 20)
  - QSL Requests 1960 Jan.-Feb. (Box 20)
  - Protestant 1960 (Box 20)
  - Religious Mail 1960 (Box 20)
  - Rural Church Services Broadcast 1960 (Box 20)
  - Salutes to Va. Counties Correspondence 1960 (Box 20)
  - Salutes to Va. Counties- Continuities 1960 (Box 20)
  - Special Events 1959-1960 (Box 20)
  - Spot Announcements 1959-1960 (Box 20)
  - Appreciation-Applause-Bouquets 1959 (Box 20)
  - Appreciation-Public Service-Complimentary 1958-1959 (Box 21)
    A27-8A
  - D-X Letters 1959 (Box 21)
  - Ferrum Jr. College Campaign 1959 (Box 21)
  - Inquiries 1959 (Box 21)
  - Listeners 1959 (Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous Mail 1959 (Box 21)
  - NBC Correspondence 1959 (Folder 21)
  - W.R.B. Personal 1959 (Box 21)
  - QSL Requests (Box 21)
  - QSL Requests 1959 July-Dec (Box 21)
  - Red Cross 1959 (Box 21)
  - Religious Fan Mail 1959 (Box 21)
  - Protestant 1959 (Box 22)
    A27-8B
  - VAB Legislative Committee 1958-1959 (Box 22)
  - Choirloft Program 1958 (Box 22)
  - W.R.B.'s Committees 1958 (Box 22)
  - Congratulations 1958 (Box 22)
  - CBS Correspondence 1856-1958 (Box 22)
  - Criticisms, Complaints 1958 (Folder 22)
  - Dialog 1958 (Folder 22)
  - DX Reception Reports 1958 Jan.-June (Box 22)
  - DX Reception Reports 1958 July- Dec. (Box 22)
  - Inquiries 1958 (Box 22)
  - Listeners-General 1958 (Box 22)
  - Miscellaneous 1958 (Box 22)
  - Missing Persons Announcements 1955-1958 (Box 22)
  - WRB Personal 1958 (Box 22)
  - Political 1958 (Box 22)
  - Religious 1958 (Folder 22)
  - Protestant 1958 (Box 23)
    A27-8C
  - Safety 1956-1958 (Box 23)
  - School Closing Information (Weather) 1958 (Box 23)
  - Special Events 1958 (Box 23)
  - Spot Announcements 1958 (Box 23)
  - Virginia A-B-Control 1955-1957 (Box 23)
  - Appreciation-Public Service-Complimentary 1957 (Folder 23)
  - WRB's Committees 1957 (Box 23)
  - Congratulations 1956-1957 (Box 23)
  - Criticisms, Complaints 1956-1957 (Box 23)
  - Dialog 1955-1957 (Box 23)
  - D-X Letters 1955 (Box 23)
  - D-X Letters 1957 (Box 23)
  - Inquiries 1957 (Box 23)
  - Listeners' Mail 1957 (Box 24)
    A27-8D
  - Miscellaneous 1957 (Box 24)
  - Bishop, Personal 1957 (Box 24)
  - Political 1957 (Box 24)
  - Religious 1957 (Box 24)
  - Baptist (Box 24)
  - Methodist (Box 24)
  - Presbyterian (Box 24)
  - Christian and Episcopal (Box 24)
  - School Closing Information 1956-1957 (Box 24)
  - Special Events 1956-1957 (Box 24)
  - Spot Annoucements 1957 (Box 24)
  - Unusual 1956-1957 (Box 24)
  - VAB Convention; VAB Meeting (W.R.B.'s notes as Secretary) 1957, 1939 June 22 (Box 24)
  - WRB's Committees 1956 (Box 24)
  - D-X Letters 1956 (Box 24)
  - Fan Mail 1956 (Box 24)
  - Inquiries 1956 (Box 24)
  - Miscellaneous 1956 (Box 25)
    A27-8E
  - Personal 1956 (Box 25)
  - Political 1956 (Box 25)
  - Religious 1956 (Box 25)
  - Baptist, Methodist, Christian and Episcopal, Protestant 1956 (Box 25)
  - Billy Graham's Richmond Mission 1956 (Box 25)
  - Religious News 1956 (Box 25)
  - Spot Announcements 1956 (Box 25)
  - WRVA-TV 1956 (Folder 25)
  - Appreciation, Public Service 1955 (Box 25)
  - CBS Correspondence 1954-1955 (Box 25)
  - Bishop's Committees 1955 (Box 25)
  - Alphabetical File of Letters 1955 (Box 25)
  - Complimentary 1955 (Box 25)
  - Funeral 1955 (Box 25)
  - Miss M. Hughes Correspondence 1955 (Box 25)
  - Inquiries 1955 (Box 26)
    A27-8F
  - Madison College, Miss Shaeffer 1955 (Box 26)
  - Miscellaneous 1955 (Box 26)
  - Lillian Morrow 1955 (Box 26)
  - Negro Churches 1955 (Box 26)
  - Religious 1955 (Box 26)
  - Baptist (Box 26)
  - Christian and Episcopal (Box 26)
  - Methodist (Box 26)
  - Presbyterian (Box 26)
  - Political 1955 (Box 26)
  - WRB Personal 1955 (Box 26)
  - Religious News 1955 (Box 26)
  - WRVA Sign-offs, Minister's Prayers (Box 26)
  - C.W. Smith Correspondence 1955 (Box 26)
  - Spot Announcements, N.C.-P.-S. 1955 (Box 26)
  - Sunshine Hour Recordings (Folder 26)
  - Unusual 1953-1955 (Box 26)
  - Alcoholic Beverage 1953-1954 (Box 26)
  - 29th Anniversary 1954 Nov. 2 (Box 26)
  - CBS Program Inquiries, Courtesy Letters, CBS material 1954 (Box 27)
    A27-8G
  - Bishop's Committees 1954 (Box 27)
  - Complimentary 1954 (Box 27)
  - D-X File 1954 (Box 27)
  - Dialog (Box 27)
  - FM- Bishop 1954 (Box 27)
  - Inter Office Memos (Box 27)
  - Miscellaneous 1954 (Box 27)
  - Missing Person Announcements (Box 27)
  - Navy Correspondence 1954 (Box 27)
  - Political 1954 (Box 27)
  - WRB Personal 1954 (Box 27)
  - WRB Personal 1953 (Box 28)
    A27-8H
  - Program Inquiries 1954 (Box 28)
  - Religious 1954 (Box 28)
  - Religious News(publication) 1953-1954 (Box 28)
  - Special Events 1953-1954 (Box 28)
  - Spot Announcements 1954 (Box 28)
- Series II: Economic and Technical Files
  - American Chicle Co. (Box 29)
    A27-8I
  - American Cigar and Cigarette Co. - Pall Mall Cigarettes (Box 29)
  - American Safety Razor Co. (Box 29)
  - Arkady Farms Milling Co. (Box 29)
  - BC Remedy Co. (Box 29)
  - Best Foods- We, the Abbots (Box 29)
  - Blue Ribbon Books, Inc. (Box 29)
  - Bristol-Meyers Co., Minit-Rub (Box 29)
  - Bulova Watch Co. (Box 29)
  - California Fruit Growers Association (Box 29)
  - Carter Medicine Co.- Liver Pills (Box 20)
    A27-8J
  - Catspaw Rubber Co. (Box 30)
  - Chattanooga Medicine Co. (Box 30)
  - Chilean Nitrate- Uncle Natchel (Box 30)
  - Cliquot Club Co. (Box 30)
  - Colgate-Palmolive-Peet Announcements (Box 30)
  - Edwards Coffee Co.- Nob Hill (Box 30)
  - Dupont (Box 30)
  - Ex-Lax Inc. (Box 31)
    A27-8K
  - Ford Motor Announcements (Box 31)
  - Foster Milburn Co.- Doan's (Box 31)
  - Gardner Nursery Co. (Box 31)
  - General Mills- Light of the World (Box 31)
  - General Mills- Guiding Light (Box 31)
  - General Motors- Chev. Division (Box 31)
  - Gillette Razor Co. (Box 31)
  - Goodyear Tire and Rubber Co. (Box 31)
  - Griffin Manufacturing Co. (Box 31)
  - L.S. Health and Sons (Box 32)
    A27-8L
  - International Salt Co. (Folder 32)
  - Larus and Bros. Co.- Edgeworth Dance Party (Box 32)
  - Thomas Leeming Co. - Baume Bengue (Box 32)
  - Lehn and Fink Products Co. (Box 32)
  - Lever Bros. Co. (Box 32)
  - Lamont, Corliss and Co. - Pond's (Box 32)
  - John F. Jelke Co. - Happy Meeting Time (Box 32)
  - Lutheran Hour (Box 32)
  - Lydia Pinkham Co. (Box 32)
  - Manhattan Soap Co.- Sweetheart Soap (Box 32)
  - Benj. Moore Paint Co.- Betty Moore (Box 32)
  - Morton Salt Co. (Box 32)
  - Musterole Co. (Box 32)
  - Nolde Bros.- Korn Kobbler's (Box 32)
  - Nolde Bros. - Forbidden Diary (Box 32)
  - Northwestern Yeast Co. (Box 32)
  - Olson Rug Co. (Box 32)
  - Packard Motor Co. (Box 32)
  - Dr. Pepper Parade (Box 32)
  - Pet Diary Co. (Box 32)
  - Peter Paul, Inc. (Box 33)
    A27-8M
  - Peter Paul, Inc. (Box 33)
  - Peter Paul, Inc.- Joseph Reed (Box 33)
  - Planters Nut and Chocolate Co. (Box 33)
  - Potter Drug and Chemical Co- Cuticura (Box 33)
  - Proctor and Gamble, General Information (Box 33)
  - Proctor and Gamble- Guiding Light (Box 33)
  - Proctor and Gamble- Ivory Bar (Box-folder 33)
  - Proctor and Gamble- Life Can Be Beautiful (Box 33)
  - Proctor and Gamble- Ma Perkins (Box 33)
  - Proctor and Gamble- Mary Marlin (Folder 33)
  - Proctor and Gamble- The O'Neills (Box 33)
  - Proctor and Gamble- Pepper Young's Family (Box 33)
  - Proctor and Gamble- Right to Happiness (Box 33)
  - Proctor and Gamble- Woman in White (Box 33)
  - Quaker Oats- Man on the Farm (Box 34)
    A27-8N
  - Railway Express (Box 34)
  - Richfield Oil Co. (Box 34)
  - Shell Oil Co. (Folder 34)
  - State Planters Bank and Trust Co. (Box 34)
  - Standard Oil Co. (Box 34)
  - Strietmann Biscuit Co. (Box 34)
  - Wene Chick Farm- Baby Chicks (Box 34)
  - Zeeman Clothing Co. (Box 34)
  - WRVA- PR Dept. Budgets, etc. 1950-1952 (Box 35)
    A27-8O
  - Budgets and miscellaneous data 1958-1962 (Box 35)
  - Controversial 1944-1957 (Box 35)
  - FCC Political ca. 1952-1960 (Box 35)
  - FCC and other Radio Law ca. 1952-1955 (Box 35)
  - Political; FCC Records and Regulations; Use of Station Time 1956-1962 (Box 35)
  - FCC, NAB; Political; Editorializing; Copyrights 1938-1951 (Box 35)
  - FCC- History of Radio Regulation 1941 (Box 35)
  - Reports to Larus Employee Meetings- W.R. Bishop 1939-1962 (Box 35)
  - Inter-Office Memos 1960-1963 (Box 35)
  - Miscellaneous Office Memos 1958-1959 (Box 35)
  - Office Memos, WRB 1954-1957 (Box 35)
  - Office Memos, WRB 1951-1953 (Box 35)
  - Office Memos 1947-1950 (Box 36)
    A27-8P
  - Office Memos 1946-1948 (Box 36)
  - Office Memos prior to 1947 (Box 36)
  - Sale of Pollitical Time ca. 1948-1962 (Box 36)
  - Political: Station Correspondence 1961-1962 (Box 36)
  - Election Campaign Data Nov. 1961 (Box-folder 36)
  - Democratic Primary and GOP Convention 1961 (Box 36)
  - Political Broadcasts 1960 (Box 36)
  - Political Miscellany 1961 (Box 36)
  - 1960 Campaign: Special Election to House of Delegates; Democratic Primary; General Election 1960 Jan 8, July 12, Nov. 8 (Box 37)
    A27-8Q
  - Political Time Sold 1960 (Box 37)
  - Political 1959 (Box 37)
  - Political 1955 (Box 37)
  - Addresses, articles, etc. 1956-1958 (Box 37)
  - Political Miscellany 1952 (Box 37)
  - Political 1946-1952 (Box 37)
  - Political 1935, 1938-1940, 1948-1949, 1952 (Box 37)
  - WRVA Job Classifications and Rates, Revisions 1939-1941, 1943 (Box 38)
    A27-8R
  - WRVA New Wood Tower- Bills 1935 (Box 38)
  - Radio Invoices- KW Station 1925 (Box 38)
  - Receipts- New Station, Mechanicsville 1929 (Box 38)
  - Ascap Audits, Carey and Tansey 1942 March 6 - 1955 June 30 (Box 38)
  - WRVA Budget 1952 (Box 38)
  - WRVA Budget 1951 (Box 38)
  - WRVA Budget 1950 (Box 38)
  - WRVA Budget 1949 (Box 38)
  - WRVA Budgets 1945-1947 (Box 38)
  - Ascap Reports, Radio Breakdown; E-2 1961-1962 (Box 39)
    A27-8S
  - Bound Financial and Legal notebooks (Box 39)
  - Sales Promotion Campaign: Pouches, Pipes, Testing Kits, etc. 1929-1937 (Box 40)
    A27-8T
  - C.T. Lucy Advertising Data (Personal) 1937 Oct 1 (Box 40)
  - Radio Script, Frank Ryan Radio Commercials 1941 (Box 40)
  - Miscellaneous Advertising and Information 1940-1965 (Box 40)
  - WRVA Station Affairs and Advertisers (Box 40)
  - Norfolk Studio (Box 41)
    A27-9A
  - Towers- Change to Series Feed 1941 (Box 41)
  - Radio- New Studies in Hotel Richmond 1933 (Box 41)
  - Graybar (Western Electric Co.) 1933-1934 (Box 41)
  - 50 KW Shunt Feed Antenna, Varina- Radiation Patterns 1939-1940 (Box 41)
  - Varina: 50 KW Building Plans and Construction 1938-1939 (Box 41)
  - FM Norfolk/WRVA-WRVC/Combined Temp. Studios: 2712-14 Corley 1949 (Box 41)
  - Varina 50 KW (Box 41)
  - Varina 50 KW (Box 41)
  - Data on Various Sites for 50 KW (Box 41)
  - Data on Radio Site at Machanicsville (Box 41)
  - FM Richmond (Ridge Road Sites) (Box 41)
  - FM Richmond, U.S. 60 Site #2 1948 (Box 41)
  - Transmitter Log (Box 42)
    A27-9B
  - Station Employee Material 1942 (Box 42)
  - Personnel Survey, WRVA 1938 (Box 42)
  - WRVA, Organization Charts (C.T. Lucy Personal File) 1934-1952 (Box 42)
  - WRVA Personnel 1933-1941 (Box 42)
- Series III: Walter R. Bishop Files 1925-1963
  - WRB's Cracker Barrel 1960 (Box 43)
    A27-9C
  - Mail and Cracker Barrel Material 1961-1963 (Box 43)
  - Cracker Barrel Material and Letters 1959-1960 (Box 43)
  - Cracker Barrel Mail 1955-1958 (Box 43)
  - Cracker Barrel #7 1962 June 2 - 1963 Jan 26 (Box 43)
  - Cracker Barrel #6 1961 Oct 7 - 1962 Jan 13 (Box 43)
  - Cracker Barrel #5 1960 Aug 6 - 1960 Dec 31 (Box 43)
  - Cracker Barrel #5 1960 April 23 - 1960 July 30 (Box 43)
  - Cracker Barrel #4 1958 April 12 - 1958 Aug 30 (Box 43)
  - Cracker Barrel #4 1959 Sep 19 - 1959 Dec 26 (Box 44)
    A27-9D
  - Cracker Barrel #3 1958 Sep 6 - 1959 Jan 3 (Folder 44)
  - Cracker Barrel #2 1957 Sep 7 - 1958 Jan 4 (Box 44)
  - Cracker Barrel #1 1955 Aug 13 - 1955 Dec 31 (Box 44)
  - George W. Rogers to WRB, Cracker Barrel, Miscellaneous Historical Material (Box-folder 44)
  - Personal Material (Box 45)
    A27-9E
  - Bishop, personal material (Box 45)
  - Bishop, personal- civic (Box-folder 45)
  - Bishop, personal- religious 1941 (Box 45)
  - Bishop, personal and business (Box 45)
  - Bishop, personal, business, insurance (Box 45)
  - Bishop, personal (Box 45)
  - Bishop and WRVA (Personal and Religious) Miscellany (Box 46)
    A27-9F
  - Bishop, Diary and ledger (Box 46)
  - Bishop, Legal pad (Box 46)
  - Bishop, Engagement Calendar 1947 (Box 46)
  - Bishop, personal and business (Box 46)
  - Bishop, personal (Box 46)
  - Clippings (Box 46)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 46)
  - Other personal material (Folder 46)
  - Map, travel material (Box 47)
    A27-9G
  - WRB- Personal notes and memos from his desk 1963 May (died 1963 May 5) (Box 47)
  - Florence Clay Bishop's Story and Poem (Box 47)
  - WRB's newspaper articles (Box 47)
  - Bishop Naval material (Box 47)
  - Bishop Naval affairs (Box 47)
  - U.S. Army, Navy, Marine, Coast Guard (Box 47)
  - U.S. Civil Service, War Assets, Disabled Vets Administration, Disabled American Vets (Box 47)
  - WRB, Navy 1950-1952 (Box 47)
  - WRB, Navy 1950s (Box 47)
  - Navy Mail 1953-1954 (Box 48)
    A27-9H
  - WRB Navy material (Box 48)
  - Navy League of the United States (Box 48)
  - WRB Navy material (Box 48)
  - Officers' Club (Box 48)
  - Bishop Financial Material (Box 49)
    A27-9I
  - Bishop Financial Material (Box 49)
  - Bishop Financial Material (Box 49)
  - Bishop Personal and Financial (Box 50)
    A27-9J
  - Bishop Financial Material (Box 50)
  - Insurance (Box 50)
  - Bishop Financial Material (Box 50)
  - Bishop Personal Correspondence (Box 51)
    A27-9K
  - Bishop Personal Correspondence (Box 51)
  - Bishop Personal Material and Correspondence (Box 51)
  - Bishop Personal and Civic Correspondence (Box 51)
  - Correspondence (mostly Bishop) (Box 51)
  - Crippled Children's Hospital (Box 52)
    A27-9L
  - Education (Folder 52)
  - Civil War Centennial (Box 52)
  - Red Cross (Box 52)
  - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 52)
  - Schools, Colleges 1942 (Box 52)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 52)
  - Public Relations (Box 52)
  - Public Interest and Service (Box 52)
  - Women's Organization (Folder 52)
  - Bishop's Organizations (Box 52)
  - Richmond First Club 1934 Oct. - 1940 Sept. (Box 53)
    A27-9M
  - Richmond First Club (Box 53)
  - Messages of Sympathy, Clippings (Box 53)
  - Personal- Station Civic Activity (Box 53)
  - Methodist Orphanage/Assn. of Mens Bible Classes, Richmond Dist. 1941-1942 (Folder 53)
  - Christmas Data- Gift Selection List (Box 53)
  - Public Relations Association Historian (Bishop) (Box 54)
    A27-9N
  - Bishop, McCue Correspondence; Bishop Financial (Box 54)
  - Bishop Committees (Box 54)
  - Richmond First Club (Folder 54)
  - Miscellany (Box 54)
  - Hilliard Park Civic Association (Box 54)
  - Richmond First Club (Box 55)
    A27-9O
  - American Legion (Box 55)
  - WRB Personal and Station Souvenirs (Box 55)
  - Virginia Chamber of Commerce (Box 55)
  - WRB- Church, Civic Activities (Box 55)
  - Trafco Workshop 1958 (Box 55)
  - Data for Possible Addresses: Stories, Poems, etc. (Box-folder 56)
    A27-9P
  - Information - General (Box 56)
  - Information- Geography, Travel (Box 56)
  - Information - Safety 1942 (Box 56)
  - Data, clippings- Richmond, Richmonders (Box 56)
  - Data, clippings- Virginia, Virginians (Box 56)
  - Clippings: People I (Bishop?) Know of Know Of (Box 56)
  - General Clippings (Box 56)
  - Letters- Data for Possible Important Reference (Folder 56)
  - Data on Civic Events- Cost of Lines for Remote Control, etc. (Box-folder 56)
  - Duties in PR Department (Box 56)
  - Bishop and the Churches (Box 56)
  - Other Trafco Data (Box 57)
    A27-9Q
  - Crippled Children's Hospital (Box 57)
  - Bishop Correspondence (Box 57)
  - W.R.B. Material 1936 (Box 57)
  - Bishop Miscellany (Box 57)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 57)
  - Church and Christmas (Box 58)
    A27-9R
  - Mail for Reply (Box 58)
  - Red Cross (Box 58)
  - Red Cross (Box 58)
  - Red Cross (Box 59)
    A27-9S
  - Red Cross (Box 59)
  - Red Cross (Box 59)
  - Red Cross (Box 60)
    A27-9T
  - Bishop Correspondence (Box 60)
  - Miscellaneous (Folder 60)
  - Red Cross (Folder 60)
  - Red Cross (Box 60)
  - Red Cross (Box 61)
    A27-10A
  - Miscellaneous (Box 61)
  - Education 1950s (Box 61)
  - Appreciation- Public Services 1951-1952 (Box 61)
  - Appreciation- Public Services 1953 (Box 61)
  - Religious and Trafco (Box 61)
  - Radio and TV clippings (Box 61)
  - Other clippings (Box 61)
  - Public Relations and connected material (Box 61)
  - Bishop- Station miscellany (Box 62)
    A27-10B
  - WRB: clippings, personal letters, WRVA mail (Box 62)
  - Unusual letters, etc. (Box 62)
  - TV, Radio, PR (Box 62)
  - Virginia Methodist Children's Home (Box 62)
  - WRB Miscellany (Box 62)
  - Cillis Church News (Box 62)
  - Educational 1948-1949 (Box 63)
    A27-10C
  - Junior Chamber of Commerce (Box 63)
  - Charity Organizations, Hospitals, etc. (Box 63)
  - Civic, Lodges, Clubs, Fraternal organizations, VFW (Box 63)
  - Richmond First Club (Box 63)
  - Richmond First Club 1958-1950 (Box 63)
  - WRB Civic Activities 1962 (Box 64)
    A27-10D
  - WRB Civic Activities 1949-1957 (Box 64)
  - Community Chest: WRB Speaker 1950-1959 (Box 64)
  - Crippled Children's Hospital (WRB- Personal) 1941-1957 (Box 64)
  - Lay Advisory Committee, Henrico County Schools 1956-1960 (Box 64)
  - Henrico County ca. 1950-1956 (Box 64)
  - WRVA Policies re: Churches, Politics, Beer 1946-1960 (Folder 64)
  - Political, WRB, Personal 1948-1963 (Box 64)
  - Prominent Richmonders, Personal Information for News Broadcasters late 1930s (Box 64)
  - Public Service Record, WRVA Radio, WRB 1941-1959 (Box 64)
  - WRB Personal Mail 1958 (Box 64)
  - Photos, WRB Personal File (Box 64)
  - Richmond First Club, WRB, Religious ca. 1942-1959 (Box 64)
  - WRB: United Givers Fund 1960-1961 (Box 64)
  - WRB: YMCA Bible Class 1954 (Box 64)
  - 25,000 Years of Va. Churches - Comp. by W.R.B. (Box 65)
    A27-10E
  - Churches, Historical Speeches and Tributes 1950-1956 (Box 65)
  - Richmond Churches: Miscellaneous Data- History (Box 65)
  - Rural Church: History, etc. (Box 65)
  - Richmond Negro Churches: History and Data (Box 65)
  - Negro Church Services 1955 (Box 65)
  - Negro Church Services 1954 (Box 65)
  - Negro Church Services 1953 (Box 65)
  - Rural Church Services 1955 (Box 66)
    A27-10F
  - Rural Churches 1954 (Box 66)
  - Thanksgiving Services- Leigh St. Baptist 1950-1960 (Box 66)
  - Church News Program (WRB) 1963 (Folder 66)
  - Church News Program (WRB) 1962 (Box 66)
  - Church News 1959 (Box 66)
  - Church News 1958 (Box 66)
  - Church News 1957 (Box 66)
  - Church News 1952 Jan. - June (Box 67)
    A27-10G
  - Church News 1952 July - Dec. (Box 67)
  - Church Services 1961 (Box 67)
  - Church Services 1960 (Box 67)
  - Church Services 1959 (Box 67)
  - Church Services 1958 (Box 67)
  - Church Services 1957 (Box 67)
  - Church Services 1956 (Box 67)
  - Church Services 1955 (Box 67)
  - Church Services (Box 68)
    A27-10H
  - Church Services for Military Bases (Box 68)
  - Church Services 1954 (Box 68)
  - Church Services 1953 (Box 68)
  - Church Services 1952 (Box 69)
    A27-10I
  - Church Services 1951 (Box 69)
  - Church Services 1950 (Box 69)
  - Protestant Bible Class Teacher's Fellowship 1952 (Box 69)
  - Va. Council of Churches, Continuities by WRB 1952 (Box 69)
  - Va. Council of Churches, WRB, Radio Chairman 1947-1951 (Box 69)
  - Church Services 1948-1949 (Box 69)
  - Religious Miscellany 1949 Jan.- June (Box 69)
  - Religious Miscellany 1949 July - Dec (Box 70)
    A27-10J
  - Church Services 1937-1947 (Box 70)
  - Church Services, Broadcasts 1938-1941 (Box 70)
  - Baptist Churches, History (Box 70)
  - Christian Churches, History (Box 70)
  - Episcopal Churches, History (Box 70)
  - Episcopal Church in Japan, History (Box 70)
  - Lutheran Churches, History (Box 70)
  - Methodist History (Box 70)
  - Presbyterian Churches, History (Box 71)
    A27-10K
  - Miscellaneous Religious Letters 1948 (Box 71)
  - WRB's Personal Religious Material 1948 (Box 71)
  - Baptist Letters 1948 (Box 71)
  - Catholic Letters 1948 (Box-folder 71)
  - Christian Letters 1948 (Box 71)
  - Episcopal letters 1948 (Box 71)
  - Hebrew letters 1948 (Box 71)
  - Methodist letters 1948 (Box 71)
  - Presbyterian letters 1948 (Box 71)
  - Religion Miscellany 1946 (Box 71)
  - Miscellaneous religious correspondence 1934-1942 (Box 71)
  - Church Services, Inquiries for Broadcasting 1941-1947 (Box 71)
  - Church Miscellany (including Station Broadcasts) (Box 72)
    A27-10L
  - Religious Folder #1 1951 (Folder 72)
  - Religious Folder #2 1951 (Box 72)
  - Religious #1 1950 (Box 72)
  - Religious #2 1950 (Box 72)
  - Religious Clippings (Box 73)
    A27-10M
  - Religious Miscellany (Box 73)
  - Virginia Council of Churches (Box 73)
  - Religious 1942 (Box 73)
  - Centenary Methodist Church (Box 73)
  - Centenary Church ca. 1952-1955 (Box 74)
    A27-10N
  - Church News 1958-1960 (Box 74)
  - Centenary Church ca. 1948-1950 (Box 74)
  - Centenary Methodist Church (Box 74)
  - Religious Material (Box 75)
    A27-10O
  - Religious Material (Box 75)
    A27-10)
  - Centenary Methodist Church 1954-1955 (Box 75)
  - Centenary Methodist Church 1954-1955 (Box 75)
  - Bishop Personal, Church (Box-folder 76)
    A27-10P
  - Religious Material 1954-1959 (Box 76)
  - Religious Miscellany (Box 76)
  - Lutheran Hour (Box 76)
  - Religious (Folder 76)
  - Station Miscellany (Box 77)
    A27-10Q
  - Bishop Political 1956 (Box 77)
  - Bishop Political 1956 (Box 77)
  - Legislative and Primary Data 1959 (Box 77)
  - Richmond City Council Election 1960 June 14 (Box 77)
  - Election Nov. 1954-1955 (Box 77)
  - Political Campaigns and Elections 1958 (Box 77)
  - Political Campaigns and Elections 1958 (Box 77)
  - Democratic Primary and GOP Material 1957 (Box 77)
  - Primary 1957 Aug 1 (Box 77)
  - Elections 1953 (Box 77)
  - Virginia Legislature 1954 (Box 77)
  - Primary (Byrd vs. F.P. Miller) 1952 July 15 (Folder 77)
  - Election 1951 Nov. 6 (Box 78)
    A27-10R
  - Primary 1949 (Box 78)
  - Virginia Legislative Data 1940 (Box 78)
  - National Political Miscellany ca. 1936 (Box 78)
  - Legislature 1950 (Box 78)
  - Legislative Proceeding ca. 1937-1947 (Box 78)
  - History, Campaigns and Elections 1930s and 1940s (Box 78)
  - More Miscellany ca. 1937-1955 (Box 78)
  - City Council, Congress 1950 (Box 78)
  - Eisenhower-Stevenson Campaign 1952 (Box 78)
  - Biographical Data on State Candidates 1937-1938 (Box 78)
  - State Political Miscellany 1932-1934 (Box 78)
  - Political Campaign 1947 (Box 78)
  - Meet Your Candidate for House of Delegates 1949 (Box 78)
  - Biographical Data, Candidates for City Offices 1947 (Box 79)
    A27-10S
  - Political ca. 1950-1957 (Box 79)
  - National Political Miscellany 1936, 1937, 1940, 1948 (Box 79)
  - Democratic Primary Data 1941 (Box 79)
  - Elections-History 1948 (Box 79)
  - Biographical Data, House of Delegates 1937 (Box 79)
  - Legislative Proceedings and Ceremony 1948 (Box 79)
  - Political Material 1937-1942 (Folder 79)
  - Political Miscellany (Folder 79)
  - Political Miscellany (Box 79)
  - General Assembly 1962 (Box 80)
    A27-10T
  - Racial (Box-folder 80)
  - Massive Resistance: Gov. Almond-Edward R. Murrow 1959-1961 (Box 80)
  - Other Political Material (Box 80)
  - WRVA Coverage of 1942 Gubernatorial Inauguration 1942 (Box 80)
  - Gubernatorial Inauguration 1962 (Box 80)
  - Gubernatorial Inauguration 1948 (Box 80)
  - Copies of Special Addresses (Box 80)
  - Presidential Campaign 1960 (Box 80)
  - Governor's Staff, WRB 1961-1962 (Box 80)